(Bernadette:)Howie, you promised you'd move.
- And I will.
- Yeah, right.
I'm not going to live in my mother's house
for the rest of my life. I'm not a child.
(Penny:)I've seen her burp you.
(Howard:)She did not burp me.
(Howard:)She was patting me on the back
and I happened to burp.
(Howard:)Don't you have other tables
you should be waiting on?
(Penny:)Yeah, but I told you, I'm not good at my job.
(Penny:)- Listen to me. He is never gonna leave.
- I'm starting to think you're right.
(Howard:)All right, I've had enough of this.
I'm a grown man. I have a successful career.
I mean, for the love of God,
I've been to space.
(Howard:)I will move out when I'm ready, and I don't
need anyone badgering me into it.
(Penny:)Wow. Excuse me.
(Howard:)That was just for her benefit. I'll move
tomorrow. I love you. Don't leave me.
Amy?